Whoa, there!
Halt!
Who goes there?
It is I, Arthur, Son of Uther Pendragon,
from the castle of Camelot.
King of the Britons,
defeater of the Saxons.
Sovereign of all England!
Pull the other one.
I am, and this is my trusty servant, Patsy.
We have ridden the length and
breadth of the land in search of knights
who will join me in my court at Camelot.
I must speak with your lord and master.
- What? Ridden on a horse?
- Yes.
- You're using coconuts!
- What?
You've got two empty halves of coconut,
and you're banging them together.
So? We have ridden since
the snows of winter covered this land.
- Through the Kingdom of Mercia. Thru...
- Where'd you get the coconuts?
We found them.
Found them? In Mercia?
The coconut is tropical.
- What do you mean?
- Well, this is a temperate zone.
The swallow may fly south with the
sun or the house martin or the plumber
may seek warmer climes in winter,
yet these are not strangers to our land.
- Are you suggesting coconuts migrate?
- Not at all. They could be carried.
- What? A swallow carrying a coconut?
- It could grip it by the husk.
It's not a question of where he grips it.
It's a simple question of weight ratio.
A five-ounce bird could not carry
a one-pound coconut.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Will you go and tell your master that
Arthur from the Court of Camelot is here.
Listen, in order to
maintain air-speed velocity,
a swallow needs to beat its
wings 43 times every second, right?
- Please!
- Am I right?
I'm not interested.
It could be carried by an African swallow.
Oh, yeah, an African swallow maybe, but
not a European swallow. That's my point.
Oh, yeah, I agree with that.
Will you ask your master
if he wants to join my court at Camelot?!
But then of course, uh, African
swallows are non-migratory.
Oh, yeah.
So, they couldn't bring
a coconut back anyway.
Wait a minute! Supposing two swallows
carried it together?
No, they'd have to have it on a line.
Well, simple! They'd just
use a strand of creeper!
What, held under the
dorsal guiding feathers?
Well, why not?
Bring out your dead!
Ninepence.
- Bring out your dead.
- Here's one.
Ninepence.
- I'm not dead!
- What?
- Nothing. Here's your ninepence.
- I'm not dead!
- 'Ere. He says he's not dead!
- Yes, he is.
- I'm not!
- He isn't?
- Well, he will be soon. He's very ill.
- I'm getting better!
No, you're not. You'll be
stone dead in a moment.
Oh, I can't take him like
that. It's against regulations.
- I don't want to go on the cart.
- Oh, don't be such a baby.
- I can't take him.
- I feel fine.
- Well, do us a favor.
- I can't.
Well, can you hang around a
couple of minutes? He won't be long.
No, I've got to go to the
Robinsons'. They've lost nine today.
- Well, when's your next round?
- Thursday.
- I think I'll go for a walk.
- You're not fooling anyone, you know.
- Look. Isn't there something you can do?
- I feel happy. I feel happy.
- Ah, thanks very much.
- Not at all. See you on Thursday.
Right. All right.
- Who's that, then?
- I don't know. Must be a king.
- Why?
- He hasn't got shit all over him.
- Old woman!
- Man!
Man. Sorry. What knight
lives in that castle over there?
- I'm 37.
- I-- what?
I'm 37. I'm not old.
- Well, I can't just call you 'Man'.
- Well, you could say 'Dennis'.
Well, I didn't know you
were called 'Dennis'.
Well, you didn't bother
to find out, did you?
I did say 'sorry' about the 'old
woman', but from the behind you looked...
What I object to is that you
automatically treat me like an inferior!
- Well, I am king.
- Oh, King, eh, very nice.
And how d'you get that, eh?
By exploiting the workers!
By hanging on to outdated
imperialist dogma which perpetuates
the economic and social
differences in our society!
If there's ever going
to be any progress...
Dennis, there's some
lovely filth down here.
Oh! How d'you do?
How do you do, good lady?
I am Arthur, King of the Britons.
- Who's castle is that?
- King of the who?
- The Britons.
- Who are the Britons?
Well, we all are. We are all
Britons, and I am your king.
Didn't know we had a king. I thought
we were an autonomous collective.
You're fooling yourself.
We're living in a dictatorship.
A self-perpetuating autocracy
in which the working classes...
Oh, there you go
bringing class into it again.
That's what it's all about. If
only people would hear of...
Please, good people. I am in haste.
Who lives in that castle?
- No one lives there.
- Then who is your lord?
- We don't have a lord.
- What?
I told you. We're an
anarcho-syndicalist commune.
We take it in turns to act as a
sort of executive officer for the week...
Yes.
...but all the decisions
of that officer have...
...to be ratified at a special
bi-weekly meeting...
Yes, I see.
...by a simple majority in the
case of purely internal affairs...
Be quiet!
..but by a two-thirds majority
in the case of more major...
Be quiet! I order
you to be quiet.
Order, eh? Who does he think he is? Heh.
- I am your king!
- Well, I didn't vote for you.
- You don't vote for kings.
- Well, how did you become King, then?
The Lady of the Lake, her arm clad
in the purest shimmering samite,
held aloft Excalibur
from the bosom of the water,
signifying, by divine providence,
that I, Arthur, was to carry Excalibur.
That is why I'm your king!
Listen. Strange women lying in ponds,
distributing swords, is no basis
for a system of government.
Supreme executive power
derives from a mandate from the masses.
Not from some farcical aquatic ceremony.
Be quiet!
Well, but you can't expect
to wield supreme executive
power just 'cause some
watery tart threw a sword at you!
Shut up!
I mean, if I went 'round
saying I was an emperor just
because some moistened bint had lobbed
a scimitar at me, they'd put me away!
Shut up, will you? Shut up!
Ah, now we see the
violence inherent in the system.
Shut up!
Oh! Come and see the
violence inherent in the system!
- Help! Help! I'm being repressed!
- Bloody peasant!
Oh, what a give-away. Did you
hear that? Did you hear that, eh?
That's what I'm on
about. Did you see
him repressing me?
You saw it, didn't you?
You fight with the strength of many men,
Sir Knight.
I am Arthur, King of the Britons.
I seek the finest and
the bravest knights in
the land to join me in
my court at Camelot.
You have proved yourself worthy.
Will you join me?
You make me sad. So be it. Come, Patsy.
None shall pass.
- What?
- None shall pass.
I have no quarrel with you, good
Sir Knight, but I must cross this bridge.
Then you shall die.
I command you, as King of the Britons,
to stand aside.
I move for no man.
So be it!
Now, stand aside, worthy adversary.
- 'Tis but a scratch.
- "A scratch"? Your arm's off!
- No, it isn't.
- Well, what's that, then?
- I've had worse.
- You liar!
Come on, ya pansy!
Victory is mine!
We thank Thee Lord, that in Thy mer...
- Come on, then.
- What?
Have at you!
Eh. You are indeed brave,
Sir Knight, but the fight is mine.
Oh, had enough, eh?
Look, you stupid bastard.
You've got no arms left.
- Yes, I have.
- Look!
Just a flesh wound.
- Look, stop that.
- Chicken! Chickennn!
Look, I'll have your leg. Right!
- Right! I'll do you for that!
- You'll what?
- Come here!
- What are you going to do, bleed on me?
-  I'm invincible!
- You're a loony.
The Black Knight always triumphs.
Have at you!
Come on, then.
All right, we'll call it a draw.
- Come, Patsy.
- Oh. Oh, I see.
Running away, eh? You yellow bastard!
Come back here and take what's coming
to you! I'll bite your legs off!
♪ Pie Lesu Domine ♪
♪ Dona eis requiem ♪
- A witch! A witch!
♪ Pie Lesu Domine...
CROWD: A witch! A witch! A witch!
A witch! We've found a witch!
CROWD: A witch! A witch!
A witch! A witch!
We've got a witch!
CROWD: A witch! A witch!
Burn her! Burn her! Burn her!
CROWD: We've found a witch! We've found a
witch! A witch! A witch! A witch!
We have found a
witch. May we burn her?
CROWD: Burn her! Burn
her! Burn her! Burn her!
- How do you know she is a witch?
- She looks like one.
CROWD: Right! Yeah! Yeah!
Bring her forward.
- I'm not a witch. I'm not a witch.
- Uh, but you are dressed as one.
- They dressed me up like this.
- Augh, we didn't! We didn't...
And this isn't my nose. It's a false one.
- Well?
- Well, we did do the nose.
- The nose?
- And the hat. But she is a witch.
CROWD: We burn her! Right! Yeaaah! Yeaah!
Did you dress her up like this?
CROWD: No! No. No. No. No. No. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yeah, a bit. A bit. A bit. A bit.
She has got a wart.
- What makes you think she is a witch?
- Well, she turned me into a newt.
A newt?
I got better.
CROWD: Burn her anyway!
Burn! Burn her! Burn! Burn her!...
Quiet! Quiet! Quiet! Quiet! There are
ways of telling whether she is a witch.
CROWD: Are there? Ah? What are they?
Tell us! Tell us!... Do they hurt?
Tell me, what do you do with witches?
CROWD: Burn! Burn!
Burn! Burn them up! Burn!...
- What do you burn apart from witches?
- More witches!
- Wood.
- So, why do witches burn?
- B... 'cause they're made of... wood?
- Good. Heh heh.
CROWD: Oh, yeah. Oh.
So, how do we tell
whether she is made of wood?
Build a bridge out of her.
Ah, but can you not also
make bridges out of stone?
CROWD: Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. True. Uhh...
Does wood sink in water?
- No. No.
- No, it floats! It floats!
Throw her into the pond!
CROWD: The pond! Throw her into the pond!
- What also floats in water?
- Bread.
- Apples.
- Uh, very small rocks!
CROWD: Cider! Uh, gra...gravy! Cherries!
Mud! Uh, churches! Churches! Lead! Lead!
A duck!
Exactly.
So, logically...
If she...
...weighs the same as a duck...
...she's made of wood.
And, therefore?
CROWD: A witch! A witch! A witch! A
witch!... Here is a duck. Use this duck.
Very good. We shall use my largest scales.
CROWD: Ohh! Ohh! Burn the witch!
Burn the witch! Burn her! Burn her!
CROWD: Burn her! Burn her!
Burn her!  Burn her! Burn her!
CROWD: Ahh! Ahh...
Right. Remove the supports!
CROWD: A witch! A witch! A witch!
It's a fair cop.
CROWD: Burn her! Burn her!
Burn her! Burn her! Burn! Burn!...
Who are you,
who are so wise in the ways of science?
- I am Arthur, King of the Britons.
- My liege.
Good Sir Knight, will you come with me
to Camelot and join us at the Round Table?
My liege, I would be honored.
- What is your name?
- 'Bedevere', my liege.
Then I dub you 'Sir Bedevere,
Knight of the Round Table'.
The wise Sir Bedevere was the first
to join King Arthur's knights.
But other illustrious names
were soon to follow.
Sir Lancelot the Brave.
Sir Galahad the Pure.
And Sir Robin,
the Not-quite-so-brave-as-Sir-Lancelot,
who had nearly fought
the Dragon of Angnor,
who had nearly stood up to
the vicious Chicken of Bristol,
and who had personally wet himself
at the Battle of Badon Hill.
And the aptly named
Sir Not-appearing-in-this-film.
Together they formed a band
whose names and deeds
were to be retold throughout the centuries.
The Knights of the Round Table.
And that, my liege, is how we
know the earth to be banana-shaped.
This new learning amazes me, Sir Bedevere.
Explain again how sheep's bladders
may be employed to prevent earthquakes.
- Certainly, sir.
- Look, my liege!
- Camelot!
- It's only a model.
Shh! Knights, I bid you welcome to your
new home.
Let us ride... to... Camelot!
♪ We're knights of the Round Table ♪
♪ We dance whene'er we're able ♪
♪ We do routines and chorus scenes ♪
♪ With footwork impeccable ♪
♪ We dine well here in Camelot ♪
♪ We eat ham and jam and spam a lot ♪
♪ We're knights of the Round Table ♪
♪ Our shows are formidable ♪
♪ But many times ♪
♪ We're given rhymes ♪
♪ That are quite unsingable ♪
♪ We're opera mad in Camelot ♪
♪ We sing from the diaphragm a lot ♪
♪ In war we're tough and able ♪
♪ Quite indefatigable ♪
♪ Between our quests ♪
♪ We sequin vests ♪
♪ And impersonate Clark Gable ♪
♪ It's a busy life in Camelot ♪
♪ I have to push the pram a lot ♪
Well, on second thought,
let's not go to Camelot.
-  It is a silly place.
- Right. Right.
Arthur! Arthur.
King of the Britons!
Oh, don't grovel! One thing I
can't stand, it's people groveling.
- Sorry.
- And don't apologize.
Every time I try to talk to someone
it's 'sorry this' and 'forgive me that'
and 'I'm not worthy'.
- What are you doing now?!
- I'm averting my eyes, O Lord.
Well, don't. It's like those miserable
Psalms... they're so depressing.
- Now, knock it off!
- Yes, Lord.
Right! Arthur, King of the Britons.
Your knights of the Round Table
shall have a task
to make them an example
in these dark times.
- Good idea, O Lord!
- 'Course it's a good idea!
Behold! Arthur, this is the Holy Grail.
Look well, Arthur, for it is your
sacred task to seek this grail.
That is your purpose, Arthur.
The quest for the Holy Grail.
- A blessing! A blessing from the Lord!
- God be praised!
Halt!
Hallo!
Allo! Who is eet?
It is King Arthur, and these are
my knights of the Round Table.
Whose castle is this?
This is the castle of my master,
Guy de Loimbard.
Go and tell your master
that we have been charged by God
with a sacred quest. If he will give us
food and shelter for the night,
he can join us in our quest
for the Holy Grail.
Well, I'll ask him,
but I don't think he'll be very keen.
Uh, he's already got one, you see.
- What?
- He says they've already got one!
- Are you sure he's got one?
- Oh, yes. It's very nice-a.
I told him we've already got one.
Well, u... um, can we
come up and have a look?
Of course not! You are English types-a!
- Well, what are you then?
- I'm French.
I'm French! Why do think I have this
outrageous accent, you silly king-a?!
- What are you doing in England?
- Mind your own business!
If you will not show us the Grail,
we shall take your castle by force!
You don't frighten us, English pig-dogs!
Go and boil your bottoms,
sons of a silly person.
I blow my nose at you,
so-called Arthur King,
you and all your silly
English k-nnnnniggets.
Thpppppt! Thppt! Thppt!
- What a strange person.
- Now look here, my good man...
I don't wanna talk to you no more,
you empty headed animal food trough wiper!
I fart in your general direction.
Your mother was a hamster,
and your father smelt of elderberries!
Is there someone else up there
we could talk to?
No. Now, go away, or I shall
taunt you a second time-a!
Now, this is your last chance.
I've been more than reasonable...
- Fetchez la vache!
- Quoi?
Fetchez la vache!
If you do not agree to my commands,
then I shall...
Jesus Christ!
KNIGHTS: Christ! Ah! Ohh!...
Right! Charge!
KNIGHTS: Charge!
Hey, this one is for your
mother! There you go.
- And this one's for your dad!
- Run away! Run away! Run away!
Thppppt!
- Fiends! I'll tear them apart!
- No, no. No, no.
Sir! I have a plan, sir.
- C'est un lapin, lapin de bois.
- Quoi?
- Un cadeau.
- What?
A present.
- Oh, un cadeau.
- Oui, oui. Allons-y.
- What?
- Let's go.
Oh.
FRENCH GUARDS: On y
va. Bon magne. Over here...
What happens now?
Well, now, uh, Lancelot, Galahad,
and I, uh, wait until nightfall,
and then leap out of the rabbit,
taking the French, uh, by surprise.
Not only by surprise, but totally unarmed!
Who leaps out?
U-- u-- uh, Lancelot, Galahad, and I,
uh, leap out of the rabbit, uh, and uh...
Ohh.
Oh. Um, l... look, i... i... if we
built this large wooden badger...
Run away!
KNIGHTS: Run away! Run away! Run away!
Run away! Run away! Run away! Run away!
- History for Schools. Take 8.
- Action!
Defeat at the castle seems to have
utterly disheartened King Arthur.
The ferocity of the French taunting
took him completely by surprise.
And Arthur became convinced
that a new strategy was required
if the quest for the Holy Grail were
to be brought to a successful conclusion.
Arthur, having consulted
his closest knights
decided that they should separate,
and search for the Grail individually.
Now, this is what they did...
Frank!
So, each of the knights
went their separate ways.
Sir Robin rode north,
through the dark forest of Ewing,
accompanied by his favorite minstrels.
♪ Bravely bold Sir Robin ♪
♪ Rode forth from Camelot ♪
♪ He was not afraid to die ♪
♪ O, Brave Sir Robin ♪
♪ He was not at all afraid ♪
♪ To be killed in nasty ways ♪
♪ Brave, brave, brave, brave Sir Robin ♪
♪ He was not in the least bit scared ♪
♪ To be mashed into a pulp ♪
♪ Or to have his eyes gouged out ♪
♪ And his elbows broken ♪
♪ To have his kneecaps split ♪
♪ And his body burned away ♪
♪ And his limbs all hacked and mangled ♪
♪ Brave Sir Robin ♪
♪ His head smashed in ♪
♪ And his heart cut out ♪
♪ His liver removed ♪
♪ And his bowels unplugged ♪
♪ His nostrils raped,
his bottom burned off ♪
♪ And his penis... ♪
That's... that's, uh... that's
enough music for now, lads. Heh.
Looks like there's dirty work afoot.
Anarcho-syndicalism
is a way of preserving freedom.
Oh, Dennis, forget about freedom.
We haven't got enough mud.
ALL HEADS: Halt! Who art thou?
♪ He is brave Sir Robin, ♪
♪ brave Sir Robin, who... ♪
Shut up!
Um, n... n... n...
nobody, really. I'm j... j...
j... ju... just, um...
just passing through.
ALL HEADS: What do you want?
- ♪To fight and...
- Shut up!
Um, oo, a-- nothing. Nothing, really.
I, uh-- j-- j-- just-- just to, um-- just
to p-- pass through, good Sir Knight.
ALL HEADS: I'm afraid not!
Ah. W-- well, actually I-- I
am a Knight of the Round Table.
ALL HEADS: You're a
Knight of the Round Table?
I am.
- In that case, I shall have to kill you.
- Shall I?
- Oh, I don't think so.
- Well, what do I think?
- I think kill him.
- Oh, let's be nice to him.
- Oh, shut up.
- Perhaps I could...
And you!
Oh, quick! Get the sword
out. I want to cut his head off!
- Oh, cut your own head off!
- Yes, do us all a favor!
- What?
- Yapping on all the time.
- You're lucky you're not next to him.
- What do you mean?
- You snore!
- Oh, I don't.
Anyway, you've got bad breath.
Well, it's only because
you don't brush my teeth.
Oh, stop bitching and let's go have tea.
Oh, all right. All
right. All right. We'll...
... kill him first and then
have tea and biscuits.
- Yes.
- Oh, not biscuits.
All right. All right, not biscuits,
but let's kill him anyway.
ALL HEADS: Right!
- He's buggered off!
- So he has. He's scarpered.
♪ Brave Sir Robin ran away ♪
No!
♪ Bravely ran away, away ♪
I didn't!
♪ When danger reared its ugly head ♪
♪ He bravely turned his tail and fled ♪
No!
♪ Yes, Brave Sir Robin turned about ♪
I didn't!
♪ And gallantly he chickened out ♪
♪ Bravely taking to his feet ♪
- I never did!
♪ He beat a very brave retreat ♪
- All lies!
♪ Bravest of the brave, Sir Robin ♪
I never!
♪ Pie Lesu Domine ♪
♪ Dona eis requiem ♪
Heh heh heeh ooh...
- Ho ho. Woa, wayy!
♪ Pie Lesu Domine ♪
- Heh heh heh heh ho! Heh heh heh!
♪ Dona...♪
- Wayy! Wayy!
♪...eis requiem♪
Forgive me, for I have sinned.
Oh!
Oooo.
Open the door! Open the door!
In the name of King Arthur, open the door!
Hello!
Welcome, gentle Sir Knight.
Welcome to the Castle Anthrax.
- The Castle Anthrax?
- Yes.
It's not a very good name, is it?
But we are nice, and we will attend
to your every, every need!
You are the keepers of the Holy Grail?
- The what?
- The Grail. It is here.
Oh, but you are tired
and you must rest awhile.
Midget! Crapper!
- Yes, O Zoot?
- Prepare a bed for our guest.
- Oh, thank you!
- Thank you!
- Thank you! Thank you!
- Thank you! Thank you!...
Away, away, varletesses!
The beds here are warm and soft,
and very, very big.
- Well, look, I... I, uh...
- What is your name, handsome knight?
'Sir Galahad... the Chaste'.
Mine is 'Zoot'. Just 'Zoot'.
Oh, but come.
Look, please! In God's
name, show me the Grail!
Oh, you have suffered
much. You are delirious.
No, look. I have seen
it! It is here in this...
Sir Galahad!
You would not be so ungallant
as to refuse our hospitality.
Well, I... I, uh...
Oh, I am afraid our life must seem
very dull and quiet compared to yours.
We are but eight score
young blondes and brunettes,
all between sixteen
and nineteen-and-a-half,
cut off in this castle
with no one to protect us.
Oooh. It is a lonely life.
Bathing, dressing, undressing,
knitting exciting underwear.
We are just not used to handsome knights.
Nay. Nay. Come. Come. You may lie here.
- Oh, but you are wounded!
- No, no. It's... it's nothing.
Oh, you must see the doctors
immediately! No, no, please! Lie down.
- Well, what seems to be the trouble?
- They're doctors?!
Uh, they... have a basic
medical training, yes.
B... but...
Oh, come. Come. You must try to rest.
Doctor Piglet! Doctor Winston!
Practise your art.
- Try to relax.
- Are you sure that's absolutely necessary?
We must examine you.
- There's nothing wrong with that!
- Please. We are doctors.
Look! This cannot be.
- I am sworn to chastity!
- Back to your bed! At once!
Torment me no longer.
I have seen the Grail!
- There's no Grail here.
- I have seen it! I have seen it!
- I have seen...
GIRLS: Hello.
Oh.
GIRLS: Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
GIRLS: Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
GIRLS: Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Zoot!
No, I am Zoot's
identical twin sister, Dingo.
Oh, well, excuse me, I...
- Where are you going?
- I seek the Grail!
I have seen it, here in this castle!
Oh, no. Oh, no! Bad, bad Zoot!
- Well, what is it?
- Oh, wicked, bad, naughty Zoot!
She has been setting
alight to our beacon,
which, I have just
remembered, is grail-shaped.
It's not the first time
we've had this problem.
It's not the real Grail?
Oh, wicked, bad, naughty, evil Zoot!
Oh, she is a bad person,
and must pay the penalty!
Do you think this scene
should have been cut?
We were so worried when the boys
were writing it, but now, we're glad.
It's better than some
previous scenes, I think.
At least ours was better visually.
Well, at least ours was committed.
It wasn't just a string of pussy jokes.
- Get on with it.
- Yes. Get on with it!
ARMY OF KNIGHTS: Get on with it!
- Oh, I am enjoying this scene.
- Get on with it!
Oh, wicked, wicked Zoot.
She must pay the penalty,
and here in Castle
Anthrax, we have but one
punishment for setting
alight the grail-shaped beacon
You must tie her down on a bed,
and spank her.
GIRLS: A spanking! A spanking!
You must spank her well,
and after you have spanked her,
you may deal with her as
you like, and then, spank me.
- And, then, spank me.
GIRLS: And me! And me!
Yes. Yes, you must give
us all a good spanking!
GIRLS: A spanking! A spanking!
There is going to be a spanking tonight!
And, after the
spanking, the oral sex.
GIRLS:
The oral sex! The oral sex!
Well, I could stay a bit longer.
- Sir Galahad!
- Oh, hello.
- Quick! Quick!
- What? Why?
You are in great peril!
- No, he isn't!
- Silence, foul temptress!
- You know, she's got a point.
- Come on! We will cover your escape!
- Look, I'm fine!
- Come on!
Wait, Sir Galahad!
No. Look, I can tackle
this lot single-handed!
Yes! Let him tackle
us single-handed!
Yes! Let him tackle us single-handed!
No, Sir Galahad. Come!
No! Really! Honestly, I can
cope. I can handle this lot easily.
Oh, yes. Let him handle us easily.
- Yes. Let him handle us easily.
- No. Quick! Quick!
Wait! Please! I can defeat them!
There's only 150 of them!
Yes! Yes, he will beat us
easily! We haven't a chance.
We haven't a chance.
He will beat us easily...
Oh, shit!
We were in the nick of
time. You were in great peril.
I don't think I was.
Yes, you were. You were in terrible peril.
Look, let me go back
in there and face the peril.
No, it's too perilous.
Look, it's my duty as a knight
to sample as much peril as I can.
No, we've got to find
the Holy Grail. Come on!
Oh, let me have
just a little bit of peril?
No. It's unhealthy.
- I bet you're gay.
- No, I'm not.
Sir Lancelot had saved Sir Galahad
from almost certain temptation.
But, they were still no nearer the Grail.
Meanwhile, King Arthur and Sir Bedevere,
not more than a swallow's flight away,
had discovered something.
Oh, that's an unladen
swallow's flight, obviously.
I mean, they were more than
two laden swallow's flights away...
...four, really, if they had a
coconut on a line between them
I mean, if the birds were walking...
Get on with it!
Oh, anyway,
on to Scene 24, which is a smashing
scene, with some lovely acting,
in which Arthur discovers a vital clue
and in which there
aren't any swallows,
although I think you can
hear a starling-- oooh!
And this enchanter of whom you speak,
he has seen the Grail?
Where does he live?
Old man, where does he live?
He knows of a cave.
A cave which no man has entered.
- And the Grail. The Grail is there?
- There is much danger.
For beyond the cave
lies the Gorge of Eternal Peril,
which no man has ever crossed.
But the Grail. Where is the Grail?
Seek you the Bridge of Death.
The Bridge of Death?
Which leads to the Grail?
- Ni!
- Ni! Ni! Ni! Ni! Ni!
- Who are you?
- We are the Knights Who Say... 'Ni'!
- No! Not the Knights Who Say 'Ni'!
- The same!
- Who are they?
- We are the keepers of the sacred words.
"Ni," "Peng," and "Neee Wom"!
Those who hear them
seldom live to tell the tale.
The knights who say "Ni"
demand a sacrifice.
Knights of Ni, we are but simple travelers
who seek the enchanter
who lives beyond these woods.
- Ni! Ni!
- Ni! Ni! Ni! Ni! Ni!...
We shall say "Ni" again to you,
if you do not appease us.
- Well, what is it you want?
- We want...
... a shrubbery.
A what?
- Ni! Ni! Ni! Ni!
- Please! Please! No more!
- We will find you a shrubbery.
- You must return here with a shrubbery,
or else, you will never pass
through this wood...
...alive.
O Knights of Ni, you are just and fair,
- and we will return with a shrubbery.
- One that looks nice.
- Of course.
- And not too expensive.
- Yes.
- Now... go!
Stop that! Stop that! Stop that!
Look on! Clear off! Go on!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
And you, clear off!
Hah. Bloody weather.
The Tale of Sir Lancelot.
One day, lad, all this will be yours.
- What, the curtains?
- No. Not the curtains, lad.
All that you can see, stretched out
over the hills and valleys of this land!
That'll be your kingdom, lad.
- But, Mother...
- Father, lad. Father.
- But, Father, I don't want any of that.
- Listen, lad.
I built this kingdom up from nothing. When
I started here, all there was was swamp.
Other kings said I was daft
to build a castle on the swamp,
but I built it all the
same, just to show 'em.
It sank into the swamp. So...
... I built a second one.
That sank into the swamp.
So, I built a third one. That burned down,
fell over, then sank into the swamp.
But the fourth one stayed up!
And that's what you're gonna get, lad.
- The strongest castle in these islands.
- But I don't want any of that.
- I'd rather...
- Rather what?!
I'd rather... just...
- sing!
- Stop that! Stop that!
You're not going into a song
while I'm here. Now listen, lad.
In twenty minutes, you're
getting married to a girl
whose father owns the biggest
tracts of open land in Britain.
- But I don't want land.
- Listen, Alice.
- Herbert.
- 'Erbert.
We live in a bloody swamp.
We need all the land we can get.
- But I don't like her.
- Don't like her?!
What's wrong with her?!
She's beautiful. She's rich.
She's got huge...
tracts o' land!
I know, but I want the...
the girl that I marry to have...
...a certain,... special... something!
Cut that out! Cut that out!
Look, you're marrying Princess Lucky,
so you'd better get used to the idea!
Guards!
Make sure the Prince doesn't leave
this room until I come and get him.
Not to leave the room,
even if you come and get him.
No, no. Until I come and get him.
Until you come and get him,
we're not to enter the room.
No, no. No. You stay in the room
and make sure he doesn't leave.
- And you'll come and get him.
- Right.
We don't need to do anything apart
from just stop him entering the room.
- No, no. Leaving the room.
- Leaving the room, yes.
- All right?
- Right. Oh, if.. if.. if, uhh..
if... if... w...
ehh... i... if... if we...
Yes? What is it?
Oh, i... if... i... oh...
Look, it's quite simple.
You just stay here and make
sure he doesn't leave the room.
- All right?
- Oh, I remember.
Uhh, can he leave the room with us?
N... no, no. No. You just keep
him in here and make sure...
Oh, yes. We'll keep him in here, obviously,
but if he had to leave
and we were with him...
No, no, no, no.
Just keep him in here...
- Until you or anyone else...
- No, not anyone else. Just me.
- Just you.
- Get back.
Get back.
- Right?
- Right.
We'll stay here until you get back.
- And, uh, make sure he doesn't leave.
- What?
- Make sure he doesn't leave.
- The Prince?
- Yes, make sure he doesn't leave.
- Oh, yes, of course.
I thought you meant him.
You know, it seemed a bit daft me
havin' to guard him when he's a guard.
- Is that clear?
- Oh, quite clear. No problems.
Right.
- Where are you going?
- We're coming with you.
No, no. I want you to stay here
and make sure he doesn't leave.
Oh, I see. Right.
But, Father...
Shut your noise, you!
And get that suit on!
And no singing!
Oh, go and get a glass of water.
- Well taken, Concorde!
- Thank you, sir! Most kind.
And again!
Over we go! Good, steady!
Now, the big one!
Uuh! Come on, Concorde!
Message for you, sir.
Concorde! Concorde! Speak to me!
"To whoever finds this note.
"I have been imprisoned by my father,
"who wishes me to marry against my will.
"Please, please, please come and rescue me.
"I am in the tall tower of Swamp Castle."
At last! A call! A cry of distress!
This could be the sign
that leads us to the Holy Grail!
Brave, brave Concorde,
you shall not have died in vain!
Uh, I'm... I'm not quite dead, sir.
Well, you shall not have
been mortally wounded in vain!
I think I could pull through, sir.
Oh, I see.
Actually, I think I'm all
right to come with you, sir...
No, no, sweet Concorde! Stay here!
I will send help as soon as
I have accomplished a daring and
heroic rescue in my own particular...
- Idiom, sir?
- Idiom!
- No, I feel fine, actually, sir.
- Farewell, sweet Concorde!
I'll, um... I'll just stay
here, then. Shall I, sir?
Yeah.
- 'Morning!
- 'Morning.
Oooh.
Ha ha! Hiyya!
Hey!
Hiyya!, Ha!
Now, you're not allowed
to enter the room... aaugh!
O fair one, behold your humble
servant, Sir Lancelot of Camelot.
I have come to take...
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
You got my note!
- Uh, well, I... I got, uh, a note.
- You've come to rescue me?
-  Uh, well, no. You see, I...
- I knew someone would.
I knew that somewhere out there,
...there must be... someone..
Stop that! Stop that! Stop it! Stop it!
Who are you?
- I'm your son!
- No, not you.
- Uh, I am Sir Lancelot, sir.
- He's come to rescue me, Father.
- Well, let's not jump to conclusions.
- Did you kill all those guards?
Uh... Oh, yes. Sorry.
They cost fifty pounds each!
Well, I'm awfully sorry.
Um, I really can explain everything.
Don't be afraid of him, Sir Lancelot.
I've got a rope all ready.
You killed eight wedding guests and all!
Well, uh, you see, the thing is,
I thought your son was a lady.
I can understand that.
- Hurry, Sir Lancelot! Hurry!
- Shut up!
You only killed the
bride's father, that's all!
Well, I really
didn't mean to...
Didn't mean to?! You put your
sword right through his head!
- Oh, dear. Is he all right?
- You even kicked the bride in the chest!
- This is going to cost me a fortune!
- Well, I can explain.
I was in the forest,
um, riding north from
Camelot, when I got
this note, you see...
- Camelot? Are you from, uh, Camelot?
- Hurry, Sir Lancelot!
Uh, I am a Knight of King Arthur, sir.
Very nice castle, Camelot.
Uh, very good pig country.
- Is it?
- Hurry! I'm ready!
Would you, uh, like to
come and have a drink?
Well, that... that's,
uh, awfully nice of you...
- I am ready!
- ...um, I mean to be so understanding.
...I'm afraid when
I'm in this idiom, I
sometimes get a bit,
uh, sort of carried away.
Now, this is the main hall.
We're going to have all this knocked
through and made into one big, uh...
- There he is!
- Oh, bloody hell.
- Ha ha ha! Hey!
- Hold it! Stop it! Hold it! Hold it!
- Hold it! Hold it! Hold it! Please!
- Ha ha!
Sorry. Sorry. You see what I
mean? I just get carried away.
I'm really most awfully sorry.
Sorry! Sorry, everyone.
He's killed the best man!
Hold it! Hold it! Please! Hold it!
This is Sir Lancelot
from the Court of Camelot, a
very brave and influential knight,
- and my special guest here today.
- Hello.
He killed my auntie!
Please! Please! This is
supposed to be a happy occasion!
Let's not bicker and argue
about who killed who.
We are here today to witness the union
of two young people
in the joyful bond of the holy wedlock.
Unfortunately, one of them,
my son Herbert,
has just fallen to his death.
But I don't want to think I've lost a son,
so much as
gained a daughter.
For, since the tragic
death of her father...
He's not quite dead!
Since the near fatal
wounding of her father...
He's getting better!
For, since her own father
who, when he seemed about to recover,
suddenly felt the icy hand of death
upon him.
Oh, he's died!
And I want his only
daughter to look upon me
as her old dad, in a very
real and legally binding sense.
And I feel sure that the merger...
er, the union between the Princess
and the brave, but dangerous,
Sir Lancelot of Camelot...
- What?
- Look! The dead Prince!
GUESTS: Oooh! The dead Prince!
- He's not quite dead!
- No, I feel much better.
You fell out of the tall tower, you creep!
- No, I was saved at the last minute.
- How?!
Well, I'll tell you.
Not like that! Not like that! No! Stop it!
♪ He's going to tell ♪
- Quickly, sir, come this way!
No, it's not right for my idiom.
I must escape more...
- Dramatically, sir?
- Dramatically.
♪ But he's here with us today... ♪
♪ What a wonderful escape! ♪
Excuse me. Could, uh... could
somebody give me a push, please?
Old crone!
Is there anywhere in this town
where we could buy a shrubbery?
- Who sent you?
- The Knights Who Say 'Ni'.
Aggh! No! Never! We
have no shrubberies here.
If you do not tell us where we can buy
a shrubbery, my friend and I
will say...
We will say "Ni."
Agh! Do your worst!
Very well.
If you will not assist us voluntarily...
- Ni!
- No!
Never! No shrubberies!
- Ni!
- Nu!
- No, no, no, no, i...
- No, it's not that. It's 'ni'.
- Nu!
No, no. 'Ni'. You're
not doing it properly. No.
Ni!
- Ni.
- That's it. That's it. You've got it.
- Ni!
Are you saying "Ni" to that old woman?
Erm,... yes.
Oh, what sad times
are these when passing
ruffians can say 'ni'
at will to old ladies.
There is a pestilence upon this land.
Nothing is sacred.
Even those who arrange
and design shrubberies
are under considerable
economic stress
at this period in history.
- Did you say "shrubberies"?
- Yes.
Shrubberies are my trade. I am a shrubber.
My name is 'Roger the Shrubber'. I
arrange, design, and sell shrubberies.
- Ni!
- No! No, no, no! No!
O Knights of Ni, we have
brought you your shrubbery.
- May we go now?
- It is a good shrubbery.
I like the laurels particularly.
But there is one small problem.
What is that?
We are now... no longer
the Knights Who Say 'Ni'.
KNIGHTS OF NI: Ni! Shh!
Shh! We are now the Knights Who Say
'Ecky-ecky-ecky-ecky-
pikang-zoop-boing-goodem-zu-owly-zhiv'
Therefore, we must give you a test.
What is this test, O Knights of...
knights who till recently said 'Ni'?
Firstly, you must find...
another shrubbery!
Not another shrubbery!
Then, when you have
found the shrubbery, you
must place it here
beside this shrubbery,
only slightly higher,
so you get the two-level
effect with a path
going down the middle.
KNIGHTS OF NI: A path! A path! A path! Ni!
Shh! Knights of Ni! Ni! Ni! Shh! Shh!...
Then, when you have
found the shrubbery,
you must cut down the
mightiest tree in the forest...
with... a herring!
KNIGHTS OF NI: A herring!
- We shall do no such thing!
- Oh, please!
Cut down a tree with a herring?
It can't be done.
KNIGHTS OF NI: Aaaaugh! Aaaugh!
- Augh! Ohh! Don't say that word.
- What word?
I cannot tell. Suffice to say,
it's one of the words
the Knights of Ni cannot hear.
How can we not say the word
if you don't tell us what it is?
- You said it again!
- What, 'is'?
No, not 'is'. You wouldn't get
vary far in life not saying 'is'.
My liege, it's Sir Robin!
♪ He's jacking it in and packing it up ♪
♪ And sneaking away and buggering off ♪
♪ And chickening
out and pissing a pot ♪
♪ Yes, bravely he is
throwing in the sponge ♪
- Sir Robin!
- My liege!
- It's good to see you.
- Now he's said the word!
Surely you've not given up
your quest for the Holy Grail?
♪ He is sneaking away and buggering up... ♪
Shut up!
- No, no. No. Far from it.
- He said the word again!
I was looking for it.
Uh, here... here in this forest.
- No, it is far from this place.
- Aaaaugh! Stop saying the word!
- The word we cannot hear!
- Stop it!
- He said "it" again!
- That's it!
Wait! I said it! I said it!
Ooh! I said it again!
And there again,
that's three "its"!
And so Arthur and Bedevere and
Sir Robin set out on their search to find
the enchanter of whom
the old man had spoken in Scene 24.
Beyond the forest
they met Lancelot and Galahad,
and there was much rejoicing.
In the frozen land of Nador,
they were forced to eat Robin's minstrels.
And there was much rejoicing.
A year passed.
Winter changed into spring.
Spring changed into summer.
Summer changed back into winter,
and winter gave spring and summer
a miss and went straight on into autumn.
Until one day.
Knights,
forward!
What manner of man are you
that can summon up fire
- without flint or tinder?
- I... am an enchanter.
- By what name are you known?
- There are some who call me...
- Tim.
- Greetings, Tim the enchanter!
Greetings, King Arthur.
- You know my name?
- I do.
You seek the Holy Grail!
That is our quest.
You know much that is hidden, O Tim.
Quite.
Yes, we're... we're
looking for the Holy Grail.
Our quest is to
find the Holy Grail.
KNIGHTS: Yeah. Yes. It is. It
is. Yeah. Yup. Yup. Hm. Mm.
And so, we're...
we're... we're looking for it.
KNIGHTS: Yes, we are. Yeah. We are. We are.
- We have been for some time.
- Ages.
Uh... uh, so, uh, anything that you
could do to, uh... to help... would be...
very...
- helpful.
- Look, can you tell us where...
Fine. Um, I don't want to
waste any more of your time,
but, uh, I don't suppose you could,
uh, tell us where we might find a,
um... find a, uh... a, um... a, uh...
A what...?
A g... a... a g... a g... a... a g...
A grail?!
Yes, I think so.
KNIGHTS: Yes. Yes. Yup. That's it.
Yes!
- Oh. Thank you.
- Splendid!
Look, um, you're a busy man, uh...
Yes, I can help you find the Holy Grail.
To the north, there lies a cave.
The Cave of Caerbannog.
Wherein, carved in mystic runes,
upon the very living rock,
the last words of Olfin Bedwere of Rheged
make plain the last resting place
of the most Holy Grail.
- Where could we find this cave, O Tim?
- Follow!
But! Follow only if ye be men of valour,
For the entrance to this cave
is guarded by a creature
so foul, so cruel,
that no man yet has
fought with it and lived!
Bones of full fifty men
lie strewn about its lair.
So, brave knights,
if you do doubt your courage
or your strength, come no further,
for death awaits you all
with nasty, big, pointy teeth.
What an eccentric performance!
They're nervous, sire.
Then we'd best leave them here
and carry on, on foot.
Dis-mount!
Behold the Cave of Caerbannog!
- Right, keep me covered.
- What with?
- Just keep me covered.
- Too late!
There he is!
- Where?
- There!
- What, behind the rabbit?
- It is the rabbit.
- You silly sod!
- What?
You got us all worked up!
Well, that's no ordinary rabbit!
That's the most foul, cruel and
bad-tempered rodent you ever set eyes on!
You tit! I soiled my armor I was so scared!
Look, that rabbit's got
a vicious streak a mile wide.
- It's a killer!
- Get stuffed!
- He'll do you up a treat, mate!
- Oh, yeah?
- You manky Scots git!
- I'm warning you!
- What's he do, nibble your bum?
- He's got huge, sharp...
He can leap about...
- Look at the bones!
- Go on, Bors, chop its head off!
Right! Silly little bleeder.
One rabbit stew comin' right up!
Look!
- Jesus Christ!
- I warned you!
- I done it again!
- I warned you,
but did you listen to me?
Oh, no, you knew it all, didn't you?
Oh, it's just a harmless little bunny,
isn't it? Well, it's always the same
- I always tell them...
- Oh, shut up!
Right!
KNIGHTS: Charge!
Run away! Run away!
KNIGHTS: Run away! Run away!...
Ha ha ha ha! Ha haw haw! Ha! Ha ha!
- Right. How many did we lose?
- Gawain.
- Ector.
- And Bors. That's five.
- Three, sir.
- Three. Three.
And we'd better not risk another
frontal assault. That rabbit's dynamite.
Would it help to confuse it
if we run away more?
- Oh, shut up and go and change your armor.
- Let us taunt it!
It may become so cross
that it will make a mistake.
Like what?
Well...
- Have we got bows?
- No.
- We have the Holy Hand Grenade.
- Yes, of course!
The Holy Hand Grenade of Antioch.
'Tis one of the sacred relics
Brother Maynard carries with him!
Brother Maynard!
Bring up the Holy Hand Grenade!
How does it, um...
How does it work?
- I know not, my liege.
- Consult the Book of Armaments!
Armaments, chapter two,
verses nine to twenty-one.
"And Saint Attila raised the
hand grenade up on high, saying,
" 'O Lord, bless this Thy hand
grenade that, with it, Thou mayest
" blow Thine enemies
to tiny bits in Thy mercy.'
"And the Lord did grin, and
the people did feast upon
"the lambs and sloths and carp
and anchovies and orangutans
"and breakfast cereals and
fruit bats and large chu..."
Skip a bit, Brother.
"And the Lord spake, saying,
'First shalt thou take out the Holy Pin.
"Then, shalt thou count
to three. No more. No less.
"Three shalt be the
number thou shalt count,
"and the number of the
counting shall be three
"Four shalt thou not count,
nor either count thou two,
"excepting that thou then proceed to three.
"Five is right out.
"Once the number three, being
the third number, be reached,
"then, lobbest thou thy Holy
Hand Grenade of Antioch
"towards thy foe, who,
being naughty in My sight,
"shall snuff it.'"
Amen.
KNIGHTS: Amen.
Right.
One!... Two!... Five!
- Three, sir!
- Three!
There! Look!
- What does it say?
- What language is that?
Brother Maynard! You are a scholar.
It is Aramaic!
Of course! Joseph of Arimathea!
- 'Course!
- What does it say?
It reads, "Here may be found
"the last words of Joseph of Arimathea.
"He who is valiant and pure of spirit
"may find the Holy Grail
"in the Castle of aaarrrrggh."
What?
"'...The Castle of aaarrrrggh'.
What is that?
He must have died while carving this.
- Oh, come on!
- Well, that's what it says.
Look, if he was dying, he wouldn't bother
to carve 'aarrggh'.
- He'd just say it!
- Well, that's what's carved in the rock!
- Perhaps he was dictating it.
- Oh, shut up.
- Well, does it say anything else?
- No!
Just 'aaarrrrggh'.
- Aaaauugggh.
- Aarrrggh.
Do you suppose he meant the Camaaaaaargue?
- Where's that?
- In France, I think.
Isn't there a 'Saint
Aaauuves' in Cornwall?
No, that's 'Saint Ives'.
Oh, yes. Saint Iiiiives.
Oooohoohohooo!
No, no. 'Aaaauugggh', at the
back of the throat. Aaauugh.
N-- no. No, no, no, no.
'Oooooooh', in surprise and alarm.
- Oh, you mean sort of a 'aaaah'!
- Yes, that's right.
- aaaaaah!
- Oooh!
My God!
It's the legendary Black
Beast of Aaarrrrggh!
That's it! That's it! Run away! Run away!
KNIGHTS: Run away!
KNIGHTS: Keep running.
KNIGHTS: Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh!
We've lost him.
As the horrendous Black Beast
lunged forward,
escape for Arthur
and his knights seemed hopeless.
When, suddenly, the animator
suffered a fatal heart attack.
The cartoon peril was no more.
The quest for the Holy
Grail could continue.
There it is!
- The Bridge of Death.
- Oh, great.
Look! There's the old man from Scene 24.
- What's he doing here?
- He is the keeper of the Bridge of Death.
He asks each traveler five questions.
- Three questions.
- He who answers the five questions...
...three questions, may cross in safety.
- What if you get a question wrong?
Then you are cast
into the Gorge of Eternal Peril.
- Oh, I won't go.
- Who's going to answer the questions?
- Sir Robin!
- Yes?
Brave Sir Robin, you go.
Hey! I've got a great idea.
Why doesn't Lancelot go?
Yes, let me go, my liege.
I will take him single-handed.
- I shall make a feint to the northeast...
- No, no. No. Hang on! Hang on! Hang on!
- Just answer the five questions...
- Three questions.
Three questions as best you
can, and we shall watch... and pray.
I understand, my liege.
Good luck, brave Sir Lancelot.
God be with you.
Stop!
Who would cross the Bridge of Death
must answer me these questions three,
ere the other side he see.
Ask me the questions, bridgekeeper.
I'm not afraid.
- What... is your name?
- My name is 'Sir Lancelot of Camelot'.
What... is your quest?
To seek the Holy Grail.
What... is your favorite color?
- Blue.
- Right. Off you go.
Oh, thank you. Thank you very much.
That's easy!
Stop!
Who approacheth the Bridge of Death,
must answer me these questions three,
ere the other side he see.
Ask me the questions, bridgekeeper.
I'm not afraid.
- What... is your name?
- 'Sir Robin of Camelot'.
- What... is your quest?
- To seek the Holy Grail.
What... is the capital of Assyria?
I don't know that! Auuuuuuuugh!
Stop!
- What... is your name?
- 'Sir Galahad of Camelot'.
- What... is your quest?
- I seek the Grail.
- What... is your favorite color?
- Blue.
No, yel... auuuuuuuugh!
Hee hee heh.
Stop!
- What... is your name?
- It is 'Arthur', King of the Britons.
- What... is your quest?
- To seek the Holy Grail.
What... is the air-speed
velocity of an unladen swallow?
What do you mean?
An African or European swallow?
Huh? I... I don't know that. Auuuuuuuugh!
How do you know so much about swallows?
Well, you have to know these
things when you're a king, you know.
Lancelot!
- Lancelot!
The Castle "Aaargh".
Our quest is at an end.
God be praised.
Almighty God,
we thank Thee that Thou hast
vouchsafed to us the most holy...
Jesus Christ!
Allo, dappy English k-niggets
and Monsieur Arthur King,
who has the brain of a duck, you know.
So, we French fellows
outwit you a second time!
How dare you profane this place
with your presence?
I command you, in the name
of the Knights of Camelot,
to open the doors of this sacred castle,
to which God himself has guided us.
How you English say, 'I one more time,
mac, unclog my nose in your direction',
sons of a window-dresser!
So, you think you could
out-clever us French folk
with your silly knees-bent,
running about, advancing behavior.
I wave my private parts at your aunties.
You cheesy lot of second-hand,
electric donkey-bottom biters!
In the name of the Lord,
we demand entrance to this sacred castle!
No chance, English bed-wetting types.
I burst my pimples at you, and call your
door-opening request a silly thing!
You tiny-brained wipers
of other people's bottoms.
If you do not open this door,
we shall take this castle by force!
In the name of God and the glory of our...
Agh. Right! That settles it!
Yes, depart a lot at this time
and cut the approaching any more,
or we fire arrows at the
tops of your heads and
make castanets out of
your testicles already!
Walk away. Just ignore them.
And now remain gone,
illegitimate-faced bugger-folk!
And, if you think you got a nasty
taunting this time, you ain't heard
nothing yet, dappy English k-nnniggets!
Thpppt!
- We shall attack at once!
- Yes, my liege!
Stand by for attack!
French persons!
Today the blood of many a valiant knight
shall be avenged.
In the name of God,
we shall not stop our fight
till each one of you lies dead,
and the Holy Grail
returns to those whom God has chosen.
Charge!
ARMY OF KNIGHTS: Hooray!!!
- Yes, they're the ones, I'm sure.
- Come on. Anybody armed must go, too.
- All right. Come on. Back.
- Get that one.
- Back. Right away.
- Yes.
- Just... pull it off. Come on. Come along.
- Put this man in the van.
- Put him in the van.
- Get a blanket over that one.
Come on. Back. Riiight back. Come on!
Run along! Run along!
Pull that off. My, that's
an offensive weapon, that is.
Come on. Back with 'em.
Back. Right. Come along.
All right, sonny. That's enough.
Just pack that in.
Christ!